[Birds chirping]
[鸟鸣声]
What does that mean, "You want more"?
你说“你想要更多”是什么意思？
Am I not enough, or...?
是我不够好吗，还是……？
You are. You know you are.
你很好。你知道的。
It's not what I meant.
我不是那个意思。
[Footsteps]
[脚步声]
So what did you mean, then?
那你是什么意思？
Just... that it's time for a change.
只是……是时候做出改变了。
So you don't believe in us, in this?
所以你不相信我们，不相信这段感情？
Just forget I said anything.
就当我说错话了吧。
My timing's always been terrible, even my mom says so.
我总是选错时机，连我妈都这么说。
'Cause you were born in the back of a taxicab during a snowstorm.
因为你是在暴风雪中出生在出租车后座的。
[Birds chirping]
[鸟鸣声]
[Footsteps]
[脚步声]
I have faith.
我有信心。
Let it be enough for both of us.
让我们彼此都知足吧。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
[Footsteps]
[脚步声]
[Indistinct chatter]
[模糊的谈话声]
Love you.
我爱你。
Love you, too.
我也爱你。
[Footsteps]
[脚步声]
[Birds chirping]
[鸟鸣声]
I ask you, what is more important, art or our planet?
我问你，什么更重要，艺术还是我们的星球？
[Gunfire]
[枪声]
Security! Security to mezzanine!
保安！保安到中层来！
We are killing our planet!
我们正在毁灭我们的星球！
We've got a defacement of progress!
我們的進展被破壞了！
The temperature of the Earth is increasing day by day!
地球的溫度每天都在上升！
Great day!
美好的一天！
Put your hands in the air!
把你的手舉起來！
Oh, hey, hey, hey!
哦，嘿，嘿，嘿！
Turn around. Let me see your hands.
轉過身來。讓我看看你的手。
Let me see your hands.
讓我看看你的手。
Hey, stop!
嘿，停下來！
Turn around.
轉過身來。
Let me see your hands.
讓我看看你的手。
[Grunting]
[咕噥聲]
Stop it, girl.
停下來，女孩。
[Gunshot]
[槍聲]
[Screaming]
[尖叫聲]
[Gasps]
[喘息聲]
[倒抽一口氣]
Donna!
唐娜！
Let's go!
我們走吧！
[Gasps]
[倒抽一口氣]
[Screaming]
[尖叫]
[Music]
[音樂]
Hey, what happened to my thumb?
嘿，我的拇指怎麼了？
[Horn honks]
[喇叭聲]
[Laughs]
[笑聲]
Dad, don't do that.
爸，別這樣。
You're gonna get him all riled up right before his nap.
你在他午睡前這樣會讓他興奮起來的。
A nap?
午睡？
We haven't even been eating yet.
我們還沒開始吃呢。
Stuart's getting the food right now.
史都華現在去拿食物了。
Right away?
馬上嗎？
You and your sister used to love when I played this game.
你和你姐姐以前很喜歡我玩這個遊戲。
Your mom would get so mad at me when I would play it just before bedtime.
每當我在睡覺前玩這個遊戲時，你媽媽都會對我生氣。
He does the same to my kids right before bedtime.
他現在也在我孩子睡覺前這樣做。
Of course he does.
當然他會這樣。
Yes, I'm gonna get his milk.
是的，我要去拿他的牛奶。
You know, Marina, your niece and nephew sure would like to get to know you better.
你知道嗎，瑪麗娜，你的姪子和姪女肯定會想更了解你。
Yes, I know, Dad.
是的，我知道，爸爸。
And I will make my way to Houston just as soon as I can.
我會盡快前往休士頓。
Well, we decided if you all wouldn't come to Houston,
嗯，我們決定如果你們不來休士頓，
then Houston would come to New York.
那麼休士頓就會來紐約。
Although why anyone would live in this city is beyond me.
雖然我不明白為什麼有人會住在這個城市。
The noise, the crazies, and the streets are dirtier than a herd of hogs.
噪音、瘋子和街道比一群豬還髒。
Okay, time to eat.
好了，該吃飯了。
Oh, sorry.
哦，抱歉。
Okay, burritos are here.
好的，墨西哥卷饼到了。
Burritos.
墨西哥卷饼。
Oh, and a turkey sandwich for Mr. Chase.
哦，还有给蔡斯先生的火鸡三明治。
Well, let me pay for those.
让我来付这些吧。
Oh, no, I took care of it.
哦，不用了，我已经付了。
Marina, your sister and I did not drive three days so that you would have to pay for our meals.
玛丽娜，你姐姐和我开了三天的车，不是为了让你付我们的餐费的。
You didn't have to drive, you know that, right?
你们其实不用开车的，你知道的吧？
There's a direct flight, Houston to New York, it's three hours.
有直达航班，从休斯顿到纽约，只要三个小时。
Well, Daddy likes to drive so he can smoke.
嗯，爸爸喜欢开车，这样他可以抽烟。
I'm well aware.
我很清楚。
You know, I'm just still impressed that you guys were able to find parking on the block.
你知道吗，我还是很惊讶你们能在街区找到停车位。
Here, I insist.
来，我一定要付。
Oh, okay.
哦，好吧。
Yeah, I'll get dinner.
对，晚餐我来付。
There's a great Japanese place just opened up down the street.
街尾新開了一家很棒的日本餐廳。
I know the owners.
我認識老闆。
Sorry, you guys are going to have to go visit the Empire State Building without me.
抱歉，你們得自己去參觀帝國大廈了。
There was a shooting at the Queens Museum, so I've got to get moving now.
皇后區博物館發生了槍擊案，所以我得趕快過去。
Well, Marina, don't worry about us.
瑪麗娜，別擔心我們。
Daddy, why? Why do you insist on calling me Marina when you know my name is Nina?
爸爸，為什麼？你明明知道我叫妮娜，為什麼堅持叫我瑪麗娜？
Well, you were my Marina when you left.
你離開時還是我的瑪麗娜啊。
Daddy!
爸爸！
All right, Marina, I got it.
好吧，瑪麗娜，我知道了。
Nina, you see, I can change.
妮娜，你看，我會改變的。
It's very impressive.
這很令人印象深刻。
Okay, we got this.
好了，我們可以的。
You sure?
你確定？
It's going to be great. Come on.
會很棒的。來吧。
Culture, sightseeing, I love you.
文化、觀光，我愛你。
Sorry.
抱歉。
I love you.
我爱你。
I love you too, thank you.
我也爱你，谢谢。
Join us for dinner.
和我们一起吃晚餐吧。
I will try.
我会试试。
[music]
[音乐]
I just got off the phone with Isabel.
我刚和伊莎贝尔通完电话。
The mayor himself reached out asking for our help finding these two shooters.
市长亲自联系，要求我们帮忙找到这两名枪手。
We need to reassure the public they can go to a museum and not end up covered in pig blood like some reenactment of Carrie.
我们需要向公众保证，他们可以去博物馆，而不会像《魔女嘉莉》的重现那样被猪血覆盖。
What do we know so far?
我们目前知道什么？
All right, so we got Emma Culp, Trevor Allen, both 28, both from New York.
好的，我们有艾玛·卡尔普和特雷弗·艾伦，两人都是28岁，来自纽约。
They're climate change activists who belong to a group called Global Climate Fund.
他们是气候变化活动家，属于一个名为“全球气候基金”的组织。
There are no strangers to public acts of defiance.
他们对公开的挑衅行为并不陌生。
Are they the ones that disrupted the performance of enemy of the people?
他们是那些干扰《人民公敌》演出的人吗？
Yes, they were also involved with the campus protests at Ridgewell College three weeks ago.
是的，他们还参与了三周前里奇韦尔学院的校园抗议活动。
So maybe the assault is a reaction, a payback for the shooting.
所以也許這次襲擊是一種反應，是對槍擊事件的報復。
A cell phone footage didn't catch them saying anything about retribution before the guard was shot.
手機錄影沒有捕捉到他們在守衛被射擊前提到任何關於報復的事情。
Maybe they didn't mean to shoot him.
也許他們並不是故意射擊他。
Yeah, they didn't take a weapon into the museum.
是的，他們沒有帶武器進入博物館。
Trevor also didn't leave the gun behind.
特雷弗也沒有留下槍。
Could be a sense of fatalism kicked in after the shooting like they have nothing left to lose.
可能是在槍擊後有種宿命感襲來，就像他們已經沒有什麼可失去的了。
We should be ready for anything with these two.
我們應該對這兩個人做好一切準備。
So they went into Corona Park. Any eyes on them since?
所以他們進入了科羅納公園。之後有看到他們嗎？
Uh, let's see.
嗯，讓我看看。
No, all the cameras in the park are down due to a recent update. Everything's offline.
沒有，公園裡的所有攝像頭因為最近的更新都關閉了。一切都離線了。
Their phones are off also.
他們的手機也關機了。
Are these two together? Trevor and Emma?
這兩個人在一起嗎？特雷弗和艾瑪？
Maybe. I went through Emma's social media.
可能吧。我查看了艾瑪的社交媒體。
She was at Pride in June. She stands for "Love is Love."
她六月份參加了驕傲遊行。她支持「愛就是愛」。
Clearly she's never been divorced. Love is expensive.
顯然她從未離過婚。愛是昂貴的。
I mean, she might have a girlfriend too.
我是说，她可能也有个女朋友。
Hmm. I wonder if she's loyal to Trevor.
嗯。我在想她是否对特雷弗忠诚。
One might flip on the other.
一方可能会背叛另一方。
Hannah, does this Global Climate Front have an office or anything?
汉娜，这个全球气候前线有办公室之类的吗？
Yes. I tracked their headquarters to Brooklyn, not far from Emma's apartment.
是的。我追踪到他们的总部在布鲁克林，离艾玛的公寓不远。
New Cycle's doing a hell of a job of boloing these two.
新周期在追踪这两个人方面做得非常出色。
You and I will go to their headquarters. Nina Ray, check on Emma's digs.
你和我去他们的总部。妮娜·雷，你去查查艾玛的住处。
They're on their way.
他们已经在路上了。
Hey, what's the latest with Barnes?
嘿，巴恩斯那边有什么最新消息吗？
She says she's back next week for sure.
她说她下周肯定回来。
Okay. See you in the car.
好的。车里见。
Okay.
好的。
So I saw Emma leave this morning with that guy on the news.
我今天早上看到艾玛和新闻上的那个男人一起离开了。
Thought maybe he spent the night. They went for a breakfast.
以为他可能在她那儿过夜了。他们一起去吃了早餐。
Okay. Do we have a sense of the people in her life? Maybe who she's dating?
好的。我们对她的生活中的人有了解吗？也许她在和谁约会？
Everything's so fluid these days, right? Girls with girls, girls with guys, girls with girls and guys.
現在一切都這麼流動，對吧？女孩和女孩在一起，女孩和男孩在一起，女孩和女孩和男孩在一起。
So that's a no.
所以這是不行。
Well, the Trevor guy's the only person I've seen around here on the regular.
嗯，特雷弗是我在這裡經常見到的唯一一個人。
Her fridge is full.
她的冰箱是滿的。
Yeah, these are two and she has a suitcase in there.
是的，這裡有兩個，她還有一個行李箱在那裡。
It doesn't look like she was going on the run that day.
看起來她那天並沒有打算逃跑。
Well, they're definitely improvising and don't have a plan.
嗯，他們肯定是在即興發揮，沒有計劃。
Do we know what Emma did for employment?
我們知道艾瑪做什麼工作嗎？
Internships mostly. Her and Trevor have a spotty employment record.
主要是實習。她和特雷弗的工作記錄都不太穩定。
Do you know if a trust fund pays the rent for this place?
你知道這個地方的租金是由信託基金支付的嗎？
So now get this. On the news, they say they're looking for an Emma Cope.
所以現在聽好了。新聞上說他們在找一個叫艾瑪·科普的人。
But her rent checks always come from a Jefferies Corp.
但她的租金支票總是來自傑弗里斯公司。
Jefferies Corporation.
傑弗里斯公司。
Yeah.
是的。
All right, so there's a Jefferies family. They made most of the money in oil.
好吧，所以有一個傑弗里斯家族。他們的大部分錢都是從石油中賺來的。
Emma's father, Alexander Cope Jefferies, died two years ago.
艾瑪的父親，亞歷山大·科普·傑弗里斯，兩年前去世了。
Okay, so her climate activist fugitive comes from oil money.
好吧，所以她這個氣候活動家的逃犯來自石油財富。
Maybe she's trying to repay some common debt, use her inheritance to raise awareness for climate change.
也許她試圖償還一些共同的債務，用她的遺產來提高對氣候變化的認識。
She goes by a different name to distance herself from her family. Wants to write her own history.
她用不同的名字來與家人保持距離。想要寫下自己的歷史。
Possibly. Thank you.
可能吧。謝謝。
Yeah, sure.
是的，當然。
Trevor. Trevor! I really think we should turn in the gun.
特雷弗。特雷弗！我真的認為我們應該把槍交出來。
Explain what happened. That it was just an accident.
解釋發生了什麼。那只是個意外。
Don't ever believe me, Adam. I'll go to jail for murder.
永遠不要相信我，亞當。我會因為謀殺而入獄。
You didn't mean to.
你不是故意的。
I know that and you know that.
我知道這一點，你也知道這一點。
All right, look, if you want to go home, go now.
好吧，聽著，如果你想回家，現在就走。
I'll head out on my own with this girl who's supposed to meet us to help get us out of the city.
我會和這個應該來幫助我們離開城市的女孩一起獨自出發。
Tori?
托里？
Yeah, yeah. Get in.
是的，是的。上車。
All right, that's her. We'll be fine.
好的，就是她了。我们会没事的。
Because if you come with me, you'll be in the fight of your life. Not just for me, but for all life.
因为如果你跟我一起，你将会面临一生中最激烈的战斗。不仅仅是为了我，而是为了所有的生命。
Or you can go back to the life that your father gave you.
或者你可以回到你父亲给你的那种生活。
The one subsidized by the rape and murder of our planet.
那种建立在掠夺和毁灭我们星球之上的生活。
I'm coming with you.
我跟你一起走。
I mean, look, we want people to pay attention to global warming, to decrease the output of greenhouse gases so that our kids might have a chance at clean air
我的意思是，看，我们希望人们关注全球变暖，减少温室气体的排放，这样我们的孩子或许还有机会呼吸到干净的空气，
and a summer where the temperature isn't over a hundred fourteen days in a row.
并且度过一个气温不会连续114天超过某个极限的夏天。
But we do not believe in communicating our message with violence. It's in our charter.
但我们不相信用暴力来传达我们的信息。这是我们的章程。
Yeah, we'll be taking this laptop.
是的，我们会带走这台笔记本电脑。
Have Trevor and Emma ever been violent in the past?
特雷弗和艾玛过去有过暴力行为吗？
No, but Trevor has a temper. Emma's way more easygoing.
没有，但特雷弗脾气不好。艾玛则随和得多。
So she's following his lead here.
所以这次她是跟着他的节奏走。
When was the last time you spoke to Emma or Trevor?
你最后一次和艾玛或特雷弗说话是什么时候？
This morning, before all hell broke loose.
今天早上，在所有事情失控之前。
You planned for this chaos to deface the artwork with pig blood. Any other stunts we should know about? Norbert?
你策划了这场混乱，用猪血玷污了艺术品。还有其他我们应该知道的把戏吗，诺伯特？
The vote next week to save the polar bears up in Alaska. We're considering a sit-in at the senator's house.
下周关于拯救阿拉斯加北极熊的投票。我们正在考虑在参议员家静坐。
Just a sit-in?
只是静坐吗？
Yes.
是的。
Do you think our fugitives are headed for D.C.?
你觉得我们的逃犯会去华盛顿特区吗？
I think they're acting recklessly. They're young, armed and dangerous. That's a lethal combination.
我认为他们行事鲁莽。他们年轻、持械且危险。这是致命的组合。
Well, I know it's not much, but this is where I grew up. Me and my main mom, and she rests in peace.
我知道这不算什么，但这是我长大的地方。我和我的主母，她安息了。
Sorry for your lost, Tori.
为你的失去感到抱歉，托里。
She'd been sick for years.
她已经病了好几年。
Everyone around these parts has been. I've had a thyroid problem my whole life.
这附近的每个人都是。我一生都有甲状腺问题。
What is it, this disgusting water?
这是什么，这恶心的水？
It's gotta be. We're on the Marcellus Shale deposit. Oil companies have been fracking this area for years.
肯定是。我们在马塞勒斯页岩沉积层上。石油公司多年来一直在这里进行水力压裂。
They should bleed us dry, get us sick and then leave. That's why I want to help you guys.
他们应该榨干我们，让我们生病然后离开。这就是为什么我想帮助你们。
I really believe in what you're doing, and I really think you didn't mean to shoot that guard.
我真的相信你们在做的事，也真的认为你们不是故意射杀那个警卫的。
Thanks. I'm really glad you're on our team.
谢谢。真的很高兴你能加入我们的团队。
I believe in you too.
我也相信你。
It's one of the companies that fractured your hand-stabbed gas and oil.
这是其中一家公司，他们破坏了你的手工开采的天然气和石油。
Um, yeah, how'd you know?
嗯，是的，你怎么知道的？
Someone in their tanker truck's go by.
他们的油罐车有人经过。
See, there goes another one.
看，又有一辆过去了。
You know, I've been noticing them the past couple days, but I don't know where they're going because all the wells around here are closed.
你知道，我过去几天一直在注意它们，但我不知道它们要去哪里，因为这里所有的油井都关闭了。
So, what's the plan now?
那么，现在计划是什么？
I was thinking we'd stay here tonight, just lay low.
我在想我们今晚留在这里，低调一点。
Yeah? Yeah, absolutely.
是吗？是的，当然。
Are you guys hungry? I could rest something up.
你们饿了吗？我可以准备点东西。
Oh, that'd be great. Also, do you have a computer I can borrow?
哦，那太好了。还有，你有电脑可以借我用一下吗？
Yeah.
有的。
Hey, I finally decoded the Global Climate Front's messaging system.
嘿，我终于解码了全球气候阵线的通讯系统。
Norbert lied to us. He had been in contact with Emma and Trevor.
诺伯特对我们撒谎了。他一直在与艾玛和特雷弗联系。
Just after the shooting, Trevor reached out to Norbert for help getting out of the city.
就在枪击事件发生后，特雷弗联系诺伯特寻求帮助离开城市。
Norbert then found someone to pick them up named Carbon Queen.
诺伯特随后找到了一位名叫碳皇后的人来接他们。
She's offering sanctuary to our two fugitives. She says she'll pick them up wherever they want.
她为我们的两位逃亡者提供庇护。她说她会在他们想要的任何地方接他们。
So, Norbert arranged for Trevor and Carbon Queen to meet outside the PATH station in Jersey City.
于是，诺伯特安排特雷弗和碳皇后在泽西市的PATH车站外见面。
Yeah, I'm accessing the cameras now. What do you think, between one and two?
是的，我现在正在访问摄像头。你觉得，大概在一点到两点之间？
Yeah, sounds about right.
是的，听起来差不多。
Alright.
好的。
There they are.
他们在那儿。
Got it.
明白了。
You're getting into a green Subaru. Run that plate.
你们要上一辆绿色的斯巴鲁。查一下那个车牌。
Okay, plates belong to a Tori Newell, 25. She lives in Clearville, Pennsylvania.
好的，车牌属于25岁的托里·纽厄尔。她住在宾夕法尼亚州的克利尔维尔。
Put a bottle out and let's get up on our phone.
放一个瓶子出来，我们开始监听电话。
I'll have Norbert arrested for aiding and abetting.
我会让诺伯特因协助和教唆被捕。
Pack a small bag. We're going to Pennsylvania, my people.
收拾一个小包。我们要去宾夕法尼亚了，伙计们。
Nice dress.
漂亮的裙子。
[Music]
[音乐]
I was up until three in the morning. Kind of 14 tankers go by.
我昨晚一直熬到凌晨三点。大概有14辆油罐车经过。
When I looked up HENCEP gas and oil, I found this.
当我查找HENCEP天然气和石油时，我发现了这个。
They're building a pipeline for liquid CO2.
他们正在建设一条液态二氧化碳的管道。
I haven't seen any pipelines around here. What's it for?
我在这附近没见过任何管道。这是用来做什么的？
It's called carbon capture. They take all the byproducts and drill it and they pump them into the ground.
这叫做碳捕捉。他们收集所有的副产品，钻孔并将它们注入地下。
Supposedly a good thing, but the reason it's taken so long is this stuff is totally dangerous and bad for the environment.
据说这是件好事，但之所以花了这么长时间是因为这些东西非常危险，对环境有害。
Is that what's in those trucks?
那些卡车里装的就是这个吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Well, where's the pipeline?
那么，管道在哪里？
Don't know that either. But I know how we could find out.
这个我也不知道。但我知道我们怎么才能找到答案。
[Music]
[音乐]
Hey. You okay?
嘿。你还好吗？
No, it's my ankle. I think it's broken. We were riding bikes and I fell off.
不好，是我的脚踝。我觉得它断了。我们刚才在骑自行车，我摔下来了。
Bikes? I don't see any.
自行车？我没看到啊。
Nice and easy.
慢慢来，别着急。
I just want to take a ride in your truck.
我只是想搭你的卡車兜風。
Stop! Stop!
停！停下來！
[Screams]
[尖叫聲]
What are you doing? You were not supposed to shoot him.
你在做什麼？你不該開槍打他的。
I didn't have a choice.
我別無選擇。
Oh my God, I think he's dead.
天啊，我覺得他死了。
We're all dying, Tori.
我們都會死的，托莉。
Hence that's been killing people with their poison for years.
多年來，他們一直用毒藥殺人。
You of all people should know that.
你應該比任何人都清楚這一點。
Come on! We gotta get out of here!
快點！我們得離開這裡！
And go where? We don't even know where the pipeline is now.
去哪裡？我們甚至不知道管線現在在哪裡。
He's got a GPS. We'll figure it out.
他有GPS，我們會找到的。
You coming?
你要來嗎？
I'll go if you will.
如果你去，我就去。
Come on.
快點。
Hey. I've got an aerial here of Tori Newell's farmhouse.
嘿，我这里有托里·纽厄尔农舍的航拍图。
Looks like clear sightlines from any approach.
看起来从任何方向都有清晰的视线。
Yeah, except there on the south side. The topography may give us some cover.
是的，除了南边那里。地形可能会给我们一些掩护。
Reach out to troupas for backup.
联系特鲁帕斯请求支援。
On it.
正在处理。
Okay, the farmhouse is on Marcellus Shale. Most of the property is.
好的，农舍位于马塞勒斯页岩上。大部分地产都是。
That land's been fract within an inch of its life.
那片土地已经被压裂得几乎无法再承受了。
Which is probably why Tori was so keen to help Trevor and Emma.
这可能就是为什么托里如此热衷于帮助特雷弗和艾玛。
They're on their way. Sorry, give me one minute.
他们正在路上。抱歉，给我一分钟。
Hey, Stuart. What's going on?
嘿，斯图尔特。发生什么事了？
I give up. Like I surrender.
我放弃了。就像我投降了。
Oh boy, what's happening?
哦，天哪，发生什么了？
You're dad. Like he won't let me pay for anything.
你爸爸。他根本不让我付任何钱。
He keeps trying to slip money into people's hands.
他一直在试图偷偷把钱塞到别人手里。
I don't get it. Like who does that?
我不明白。谁会这样做？
Yeah, I mean that's just dad.
是啊，我是說這就是老爸。
Yeah, well I mean more than that, he keeps smoking.
是啊，不過我是說不止這樣，他一直在抽煙。
Like every 15 minutes we gotta stop so we can smoke.
每15分鐘我們就得停下來讓他抽煙。
It's New York City. There's no place to smoke anymore.
這裡是紐約市，現在根本沒地方可以抽煙了。
Can Tink help at all?
丁克能幫上忙嗎？
I mean she offered to take him to a matinee at the Lion King, but you know what?
我是說她提議帶他去看《獅子王》的日場演出，但你知道嗎？
She knows full well that they're gonna have to leave 10 minutes in,
她很清楚他們10分鐘後就得離開，
'cause he's gotta go smoke.
因為他得去抽煙。
Let me scout. When?
讓我去偵查一下。什麼時候？
We're on our way.
我們正在路上。
Our climate activist just hijacked an oil tanker truck.
我們的氣候活動家剛剛劫持了一輛油罐車。
Driver's dead. Let's roll.
司機死了，我們出發吧。
Hey, sorry, I gotta go.
嘿，抱歉，我得走了。
You know what? Take dad to Central Park.
你知道嗎？帶老爸去中央公園吧。
They have penguins and that will entertain him. He loves them.
那裡有企鵝，他會很開心的。他超愛企鵝。
Okay, I'll run up by Tink. I love you.
好的，我會去找Tink。我愛你。
Love you too.
我也愛你。
What's it say?
上面寫什麼？
Tank capacity 6,000 gallons of carbon dioxide.
罐容量為6,000加侖的二氧化碳。
6,000? That's insane.
6,000？這太瘋狂了。
Yeah, contains gas under pressure, may explode if heated,
是的，裡面裝有高壓氣體，加熱可能會爆炸，
may displace oxygen and cause rapid suffocation.
可能會取代氧氣並導致快速窒息。
But there's oxygen masks in the jockey box.
但車廂裡有氧氣面罩。
Where's that GPS say this rig was headed?
GPS顯示這輛車要去哪裡？
Something called a transfer station, whatever that is.
一個叫轉運站的地方，不管那是什麼。
Emma, take a picture of that map.
Emma，拍一下那張地圖。
We got cops on our tail. Oh, oh, my God.
我們被警察跟上了。哦，天啊。
Clear vehicle to the side.
讓車靠邊。
They want us to pull over.
他們要我們靠邊停車。
I know they do.
我知道他們要我們停車。
But we cannot run them in this heat. Let me think.
但我们不能在这么热的天气下运行它们。让我想想。
Clear vehicle over now.
现在清空车辆。
Clear down.
清空下方。
[sirens wailing]
[警笛声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[alarm rings]
[警报声响起]
[tires screech]
[轮胎摩擦声]
Tori, where are you?
托里，你在哪里？
I don't know. I don't even know.
我不知道。我甚至不知道。
Driver of the vehicle, stop the engine.
车辆的司机，请关闭引擎。
Tori, Tori, I need you.
托里，托里，我需要你。
Now exit the vehicle one at a time, nice and slow, hands in the air.
现在请一个接一个地慢慢下车，双手举高。
Tori, look at me. It has to be you.
托里，看着我。必须是你。
None of us can go out there.
我们中没有人能出去。
Okay, okay, okay. I'll go, I'll go, I'll go.
好的，好的，好的。我去，我去，我去。
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
不要开枪！不要开枪！
Face down on the ground! Okay, okay, okay, okay.
趴在地上！好的，好的，好的，好的。
Next passenger, exit the vehicle slowly with your hands...
下一位乘客，慢慢下车，双手...
They're running!
他们在跑！
Stay down and don't move.
趴下，不要动。
Tripple, what are we doing?
特里普，我们在做什么？
Is that an intermission to the world?
这是世界的插曲吗？
Freeze right there!
别动！
[gunshot]
[枪声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- Take your mask off! - What happened to Tori?
- 摘掉你的面具！ - 托里怎么了？
It's Leva!
是莱瓦！
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
[gunshots]
[枪声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
NSTEP equips all its tanker trucks with a panic button.
NSTEP公司为所有油罐车配备了紧急按钮。
It radios that location to the nearest dispatch.
它会将位置信息发送给最近的调度中心。
Who was the truck carrying?
这辆卡车装载了什么？
According to the company,
根据公司说法，
6,000 gallons of compressed carbon dioxide.
是6000加仑的压缩二氧化碳。
[radio chatter]
[无线电通话声]
Where's this apple seat corner?
苹果座位角落在哪里？
Right over there.
就在那边。
What's that?
那是什么？
Wild gas. That's for carbon dioxide.
那是二氧化碳的排气口。
[radio chatter]
[无线电通话声]
[tires squealing]
[轮胎摩擦声]
What the hell?
怎么回事？
- What's going on? - I don't know.
- 发生什么事了？ - 我不知道。
I'm pushing the accelerator, but I have no power.
我在踩油门，但是车没有动力。
It's the CO2.
是二氧化碳。
It eliminates oxygen so the engine can't combust.
它消耗了氧气，所以引擎无法燃烧。
The same thing is happening to us.
同样的事情也发生在我们身上。
[shouting]
[喊叫]
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
Cover me!
掩护我！
[shouting]
[喊叫]
We need to help these people!
我们需要帮助这些人！
Grab your masks!
拿上你的面罩！
Ray!
雷！
See if we can stop that steve!
看看我们能不能阻止那个史蒂夫！
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
[shouting]
[喊叫]
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
Cover your mouth.
捂住你的嘴。
One second, one second.
等一下，等一下。
Come, come this way.
过来，往这边走。
[shouting]
[喊叫]
Let's go, let's run!
走吧，快跑！
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
Come, come, come, let's go.
来，来，来，我们走吧。
Help! Please help us!
救命！请救救我们！
Please help us, please!
请救救我们，求求你们！
Hurry, please!
快点，求求你们！
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
[shouting]
[喊叫]
There's a guy over there, throw him in!
那边有个人，把他扔进去！
[shouting]
[喊叫]
I need help!
我需要帮助！
Please help!
请帮帮我！
I can't get her to wake up!
我无法让她醒来！
Please hurry, hurry her!
请快点，快点救她！
She's not moving!
她不动了！
[crying]
[哭泣]
Please!
拜托！
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
Clouds dissipated.
云层散去了。
We got no fatalities, which is a minor miracle.
我们没有人员死亡，这算是个小小的奇迹。
What about the trooper that was shot?
那个被击中的士兵怎么样了？
He's gonna make it too. You good?
他也会没事的。你还好吗？
Yeah.
是啊。
Look who we found hiding in the parking lot.
看看我們在停車場發現誰躲在那裡。
Toy? It was so scary.
托伊？真是太可怕了。
Where are they going? I don't know.
他們要去哪裡？我不知道。
Cover. Oh my god, you're arresting me?
完了。天啊，你們要逮捕我？
Yeah, you helped out two fugitives.
沒錯，你幫助了兩個逃犯。
You'll be helping yourself stay out of prison if you tell us where they're going.
如果你告訴我們他們要去哪，你就能幫自己避免坐牢。
Okay, it's just Trevor, it's not Emma, they're looking for the pipeline.
好吧，只有崔佛，沒有艾瑪，他們在找輸油管。
What pipeline?
什麼輸油管？
And Steph has a CO2 pipeline around here.
史蒂夫在這附近有一條二氧化碳輸油管。
I don't know, I don't know.
我不知道，我真的不知道。
That's why Trevor wanted to kidnap the truck driver so that we could find out where he was going.
這就是為什麼崔佛想綁架卡車司機，這樣我們就能知道他要去哪。
Two people matching Trevor and Emma's description just hijacked a raft for it from a white female.
有兩個人符合崔佛和艾瑪的特徵，剛剛從一位白人女性那裡搶了一艘橡皮艇。
Yeah, Walmart parking lot 12 miles away.
對，在12英里外的沃爾瑪停車場。
Check it out.
去查查看。
Sit on that curb and don't say a word, I'm not done with you.
坐在那个路边，别说话，我还没跟你完事。
Okay, she's not wrong.
好吧，她没说错。
Hen's step have just opened a CO2 pipeline that went online a week ago.
亨的步骤公司刚刚开通了一条一周前上线的二氧化碳管道。
Then we need to get them to shut it down.
那我们需要让他们把它关掉。
It could be Trevor and Emma's next target.
这可能是特雷弗和艾玛的下一个目标。
Where's their HQ?
他们的总部在哪里？
It's north in El Tuna on Highway 220.
在北部埃尔图纳的220号公路上。
Text me the address and grill the hell out of her.
把地址发给我，然后好好拷问她。
I don't know anything else, I swear.
我发誓，我真的不知道别的了。
Guess what, I don't believe a word that comes out of your mouth.
你知道吗，你说的每一句话我都不信。
Call me if you hear anything from Ray or Nina.
如果你从雷或妮娜那里听到什么，打电话给我。
Do you know how long it took us to get that thing up and running?
你知道我们花了多久才把那东西建好并运行起来吗？
Seven years.
七年。
I'm not shutting it down now based on a hunch.
我现在不会因为一个猜测就把它关掉。
It's more than a hunch, we know our two fugitives are targeting your pipeline.
这不仅仅是个猜测，我们知道那两个逃犯正瞄准你的管道。
Where?
在哪裡？
Don't know yet.
還不知道。
It's over 70 miles long, Agent Scott.
這條管道超過70英里長，史考特探員。
Except for the part over near Everett that's still under construction.
除了靠近埃弗里特的那段還在建設中。
Is that what you're talking about?
你說的是這個嗎？
It's just temporary until we finish.
這只是暫時的，等我們完工就好了。
We're really doing the residents here a favor with our carbon capture.
我們的碳捕捉技術真的對這裡的居民有好處。
What are you getting some kind of tax break for all this?
你做這些是不是為了某種稅收減免？
Damn right.
當然是。
It's called a 45Q, and after all the money we've invested,
這叫45Q稅收抵免，畢竟我們已經投入了大量資金，
I need this pipeline to be operational before the whole company goes under.
我需要這條管道在整個公司倒閉之前投入運營。
You know what happens if they blow that pipeline, right?
你知道如果他們炸掉那條管道會發生什麼嗎？
Lots of people will die.
很多人會死。
My hands are really tied here.
我真的束手無策。
Where are your priorities, man?
你的優先事項到底是什麼，老兄？
If you don't shut down the pipeline,
如果你不关闭输油管道，
you're not going to get your hands on the pipeline.
你就别想碰这个管道。
You're going to get your hands on the pipeline.
你会得到这个管道的控制权。
Where are your priorities, man?
你的重点在哪里，老兄？
If you don't shut that pipeline down,
如果你不关闭那个管道，
you think Exxon Valdez was bad?
你以为埃克森·瓦尔迪兹事件就很糟糕了吗？
Exxon survived significant challenges, and so will we.
埃克森经历了重大挑战，我们也能挺过去。
Look, I'll get these photos over to our security team
听着，我会把这些照片交给我们的安全团队，
and make sure everyone's aware of the threat.
确保每个人都意识到这个威胁。
I'm sorry,
我很抱歉，
but I'm not going to be intimidated by a bunch of pissant eco-terrorists.
但我不会被一群微不足道的生态恐怖分子吓倒。
Show me the map of the pipeline.
给我看管道的地图。
What?
什么？
I'm done playing with you.
我不想再跟你玩了。
Show me the map!
给我看地图！
[music]
[音樂]
A white buffalo was born at Yellowstone.
黃石公園誕生了一頭白色水牛。
White buffalo?
白色水牛？
Yeah, it's a sign that the Earth is at a crossroads.
是的，這是一個地球正處於十字路口的徵兆。
What is that?
那是什麼意思？
Kind of dancing with wolves thing?
像是《與狼共舞》那種東西嗎？
Tatanka, tatanka!
塔坦卡，塔坦卡！
It's Lakota.
這是拉科塔語。
Jeez.
天啊。
It's a sign that there's hope,
這是一個希望的徵兆，
but that more must be done to protect the Earth.
但也意味著我們必須做更多來保護地球。
Huh.
嗯。
Well,
好吧，
then I'd say that
那我會說
this white buffalo's right on time.
這頭白色水牛來得正是時候。
Look at how much we've accomplished so far.
看看我們到目前為止完成了多少事。
Two people are dead because of us.
因為我們，有兩個人死了。
And they've brought attention to us.
而且他們已經引起了對我們的關注。
To our mission.
對我們的使命的關注。
Over the news, everyone's talking about us.
新聞上，每個人都在談論我們。
Don't you see how great that is?
你不覺得這有多棒嗎？
How else are we going to change the world?
我們還能怎麼改變世界？
Save the world.
拯救世界。
You see it, right?
你明白的，對吧？
Violence is the answer.
暴力就是答案。
Why else
不然為什麼
was that baby white buffalo born today?
今天那隻白色小水牛會出生？
Right now.
就在現在。
If not a sign that we are on the right path.
如果不是一個我們走在正確道路上的徵兆。
Yeah, I guess so.
是啊，我想是吧。
Emma?
艾玛？
Do you pledge allegiance to our planet?
你愿意宣誓效忠我们的星球吗？
To the destruction of companies
向那些将会强奸并谋杀她的公司
who will rape and murder her?
的毁灭宣誓？
I do.
我愿意。
I do too.
我也愿意。
Emma.
艾玛。
None of you are the world's attention.
你们都不是世界的焦点。
Let's show them how dangerous
让我们向他们展示这些管道
these pipelines really are.
到底有多危险。
How?
怎么做？
Remember what that warning on the truck visor said?
还记得卡车遮阳板上的警告吗？
Danger.
危险。
If heated, might explode.
如果加热，可能会爆炸。
So we're going to heat up the pipeline?
所以我们要加热管道吗？
And take a picture of the GPS
并且给GPS拍张照片
so we know where the transfer station is.
这样我们就知道转运站在哪里了。
Everything else we need we have right here.
我们需要的其他东西都在这里。
Anna, you hear anything?
安娜，你听到什么了吗？
Hey, we just got back.
嘿，我们刚回来。
Look, no cameras in the Walmart parking lot,
看，沃尔玛停车场没有摄像头，
but a witness did see Emma and Trevor.
但有目击者看到了艾玛和特雷弗。
I got something from Tori though.
不过我从托丽那里得到了一些信息。
She said that Emma took a picture of the GPS
她说艾玛拍了卡车里GPS的照片
in the truck and it was heading to a transfer station
并且它正前往管道上的一个转运站。
on the pipeline.
我亲自检查了一下，确实如此。
I checked it myself and there it was.
我已经通知了州警察，
I've alerted the state police that that's where
艾玛和特雷弗很可能正前往那里。
Emma and Trevor are probably heading.
【翻譯失敗】
Maybe, but I'm more worried about the injection well.
也許吧，但我更擔心的是注入井。
How come?
怎麼說？
It's where the pipeline terminates. All the CO2 in the line
那是管道的終點。管道中的所有二氧化碳
gets injected underground into the old shale formations
都會被注入地下的舊頁岩層中
for storage.
進行儲存。
How much CO2 are we talking?
我們在談論多少二氧化碳？
Hundreds of thousands of gallons, all under high pressure.
數十萬加侖，全都處於高壓狀態。
If they blow it there, it's just not the pipeline
如果他們在那裡引爆，不僅僅是管道
that goes. It could be the whole damn county.
會完蛋。整個該死的縣都可能遭殃。
So what's the plan?
那計劃是什麼？
Let's put up. Bray, Hannah, take the transfer station.
我們行動吧。布雷、漢娜，你們負責轉運站。
Nina and I will take the injection well.
尼娜和我負責注入井。
I'm ready people. Let's move.
大家準備好了。出發吧。
Hey there.
嘿，你好。
Agent Hannah Gibson.
我是漢娜·吉布森探員。
Officer Jackson.
杰克逊警官。
Yeah, Agent Ray Cannon.
是的，雷·坎农探员。
So what we got here?
我们这里有什么发现？
What's going on around this room?
这个房间周围发生了什么？
I haven't seen anything.
我什么都没看到。
And you sent anyone out?
你派人出去了吗？
I'm controlling the area. I haven't seen anyone.
我在控制这个区域。我没看到任何人。
Okay, cool.
好的，明白了。
This is where that tanker was headed.
这就是那辆油罐车要去的地方。
But the police.
但是警察。
Emma, you know, obviously this isn't gonna work.
艾玛，你知道的，显然这行不通。
Change of plans.
计划有变。
Let's see where this pipeline ends.
让我们看看这条管道的终点在哪里。
Why? It's gotta go underground somewhere
为什么？它肯定会在某个地方进入地下
in this whole point of carbon capture.
在整个碳捕获的过程中。
It's a better target than this ever was.
這比之前的目標好多了。
Trevor, are you serious?
崔佛，你是認真的嗎？
Grab a gas can. Let's go.
拿個汽油罐，我們走。
Trevor!
崔佛！
This will be our coup de grace.
這將是我們的致命一擊。
This is why we put on this earth, Emma.
這就是我們存在的意義，艾瑪。
We'll go through the woods.
我們會穿過樹林。
Once we're out of sight, we'll cross over.
一旦我們離開視線，我們就穿過去。
What is this?
這是什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Well, are there even two ends to this stupid thing?
這蠢東西真的有兩端嗎？
Emma, I didn't design it. I don't know.
艾瑪，這不是我設計的，我不知道。
Can we take a break?
我們能休息一下嗎？
These things are really heavy.
這些東西真的很重。
Yeah.
是啊。
I gotta go to the bathroom.
我得去洗手间。
Trevor, just pee right here.
特雷弗，就在这里尿吧。
I don't have to pee.
我不需要尿尿。
You okay, young lady?
你还好吗，小姐？
Yeah. Sorry, I was just out for a hike
嗯。抱歉，我只是出来远足，
and I guess I got lost.
然后好像迷路了。
Are those yours?
那些是你的吗？
What?
什么？
The gas cans.
那些汽油罐。
Why are you here?
你为什么在这里？
I'm here to see Trevor.
我来见特雷弗。
You're not alone.
你不是一个人。
I'm here to see Trevor.
我来见特雷弗。
我来这里是为了见特雷弗。
I'm here to see Trevor.
Why are you here?
你为什么来这里？
Wait.
等等。
You're her. The girl in the picture.
你就是她。照片里的那个女孩。
Stay right where you are.
待在原地别动。
Stop right there. Don't turn around. Go to the ground.
就停在那里。别转身。趴到地上。
Gee, I'm holstered up by the injection well.
天哪，我被注射井旁边的枪指住了。
Radio 2.
无线电2号。
Where does this pipeline end?
这条管道通向哪里？
Back that way. Four miles.
往那边走。四英里。
Where does that one go?
那条管道通向哪里？
None of your business.
不关你的事。
You think I'm messing around?
你以为我在开玩笑吗？
Okay, please, please, okay. I have a son.
好吧，求求你了，求求你了，好吧。我有个儿子。
Then answer the question.
然後回答問題。
Which of these pipelines leads to the end?
這些管道中哪一條通向終點？
This one.
這一條。
Back at the injection well.
回到注入井。
We'll take that one.
我們走那一條。
Grab the gas cans.
拿上汽油罐。
Go.
走。
Start walking.
開始走。
Get moving.
動起來。
Let's go.
我們走。
Chief, this is Smolin. FBI's here.
長官，我是斯莫林。FBI來了。
Copy.
收到。
Hey, Agent Chase, Agent Scott.
嘿，蔡斯探員，斯科特探員。
I'm all Smolin. Heard you were coming.
我是斯莫林。听说你要来。
Did you see the injection well?
你看到注入井了吗？
I thought it'd be bigger.
我以为它会更大一些。
Is it operational?
它在运行吗？
Yes, ma'am. Went online two weeks ago.
是的，女士。两周前上线了。
How come the pressure valve says zero and I don't hear anything?
为什么压力阀显示为零，而且我听不到任何声音？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Management handles all that. I'm just security.
管理层负责所有这些。我只是保安。
Can I call my boss? Why don't you do that, Miles?
我能打电话给我的老板吗？你为什么不打呢，迈尔斯？
Chief, this is Smolin.
头儿，我是斯莫林。
FBI's down here asking about the pipeline.
FBI在这里询问关于管道的事。
If it's turned on.
它是否已经开启。
Chief, do you copy?
头儿，你听到了吗？
That's weird. What?
这很奇怪。什么？
Tried to reach him a few minutes ago, but he didn't answer then either.
几分钟前我试图联系他，但他那时也没接。
Where is he?
他在哪裡？
Out patrolling the pipeline. Campbell's orders.
在外面巡邏管道。是坎貝爾的命令。
Talk to me, Ray.
跟我說說，雷。
Hey, look, Emma and Trevor were here at the transfer station.
嘿，聽著，艾瑪和特雷弗曾在轉運站這裡。
We did a perimeter search and we found the Toyota.
我們進行了周邊搜索，找到了那輛豐田車。
Any idea which direction they went?
知道他們往哪個方向去了嗎？
No. State police didn't see either of them.
不知道。州警也沒有看到他們中的任何一個。
All right, hang on a sec.
好的，稍等一下。
It's seven miles from the transfer station to the injection well.
從轉運站到注入井有七英里。
Assuming that they're tracking the pipeline,
假設他們在沿著管道追蹤，
they should be somewhere in between.
他們應該是在兩者之間的某個地方。
On foot and armed?
徒步且攜帶武器？
We're leaving now. You should do the same.
我們現在出發。你也應該這樣做。
We'll meet in the middle and box them in.
我們在中間會合，把他們包圍起來。
Copy that.
收到。
Come on. I'm taking your Jeep.
来吧，我要开走你的吉普车。
Is your boss's Jeep?
这是你老板的吉普车吗？
Yes, sir.
是的，长官。
Anything?
有什么发现吗？
No, nothing. You?
不，什么都没有。你呢？
Where's this go?
这条路通向哪里？
I don't know.
我不知道。
What do you mean you don't know?
你说你不知道是什么意思？
Look, I'm sorry I never come down here and I've never seen it before.
听着，抱歉我从来没来过这里，以前也没见过这条路。
Only the chief patrols this area.
只有警长会巡逻这个区域。
It's not on the map.
地图上没有这条路。
Radio the other state police and tell them to get the hell down here.
用无线电联系其他州警，让他们赶紧过来。
Unbelievable.
真是难以置信。
Are you pumping CO2 into this well?
你在往这口井里注入二氧化碳吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm not sure.
我不确定。
You're fracking with CO2.
你们在用二氧化碳进行水力压裂。
I don't know what the...
我不知道这是什么……
What are you talking about?
你们在说什么？
Usually they frack these wells with water and a bunch of chemicals.
通常他们会用水和一堆化学品来压裂这些井。
But if they're using CO2 here,
但如果他們在這裡使用二氧化碳，
it's gotta be way worse.
情況肯定會更糟。
It's gotta be way worse.
肯定會更糟。
Is that even legal?
這樣做合法嗎？
I don't know anything about it.
我對此一無所知。
Mr. Campbell told me to keep this place a secret.
坎貝爾先生讓我對這個地方保密。
Hell yeah he did.
他當然會這麼說。
There's no way they have a permit for this.
他們不可能有許可證來做這種事。
[music]
[音樂]
This is a gift, Emma.
這是個禮物，艾瑪。
This is what we're gonna set on fire.
這就是我們要點燃的東西。
No! We'll all die!
不！我們都會死的！
Baby...
寶貝...
We cannot do that.
我們不能這麼做。
What happens if it explodes?
如果它爆炸了怎麼辦？
Catastrophic.
灾难性的。
Come on.
来吧。
Alright.
好吧。
Let's build this fire.
我们来生火吧。
Trevor, I can't.
特雷弗，我做不到。
We got this, Emma.
我们能行的，艾玛。
Just keep the gun on him.
只要把枪对准他。
Shoot him if he tries anything.
如果他有什么动作，就开枪。
That boy's crazy.
那小子疯了。
He gonna get us all killed.
他会害死我们所有人的。
He gonna get you killed.
他会害死你的。
Sorry.
抱歉。
Please.
求你了。
[music]
[音乐]
[音樂]
Whatever happens,
無論發生什麼，
this has been fun.
這都很有趣。
What?
什麼？
[gunshot]
[槍聲]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Release the hostage and surrender.
釋放人質並投降。
No, don't shoot me. Please don't shoot me.
不，不要開槍打我。請不要開槍打我。
Listen to him, Emma.
聽他的，艾瑪。
Ray Hanna.
雷·漢納。
Handle the fire.
處理火災。
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
I'm not doing the same of you. This is an innocent man here.
我不會像你一樣。這裡有個無辜的人。
Killing him is not going to save the planet.
殺了他並不會拯救地球。
At least his death will be linked to me.
至少他的死會與我有關。
To what I believe in.
为了我所相信的一切。
That these pipelines, the drilling, the fracking
这些管道、钻探、水力压裂
is causing our planet to burn up.
正在让我们的星球燃烧殆尽。
I'm just as worried about all this as you are, Emma.
我和你一样担心这一切，艾玛。
Your generation has left a mess for mine.
你们这一代给我们这一代留下了烂摊子。
Your driver's dead.
你的司机死了。
What else do I have to live for?
我还有什么活下去的理由？
Even that little white buffalo?
甚至连那只小白水牛？
The sign of a better time to come?
那个美好未来的象征？
It died.
它也死了。
The Earth is doomed.
地球注定要毁灭。
You really believe that?
你真的相信吗？
You wouldn't be fighting so hard to save it?
如果不是这样，你为什么还要这么拼命拯救它？
Emma.
艾玛。
You can do a lot more alive than you can dead.
活着比死了能做更多的事情。
I know your family made its money in oil.
我知道你们家是靠石油发家的。
But you can carve out a different identity for yourself.
但你可以为自己开创一个不同的身份。
Yes, you can.
是的，你可以。
Away from your father, away from it all.
远离你的父亲，远离这一切。
You can put an end to oil wells like this.
你可以终结像这样的油井。
Violence isn't the answer. Just hand me the gun.
暴力不是解决办法。把枪交给我吧。
It's over.
一切都结束了。
Come on.
来吧。
[crying]
[哭泣]
You're under arrest for domestic terrorism
你因国内恐怖主义被捕，
and accomplished a murder.
并犯下了谋杀罪。
Let's go, Patty Hearst.
走吧，帕蒂·赫斯特。
[crying]
[哭泣]
What is this exactly?
这到底是什么？
Salmon sushi.
三文鱼寿司。
How do they go past?
他們是怎麼過去的？
It's delicious, Daddy. Try it.
很好吃，爸爸。試試看。
You eat fish all the time.
你總是吃魚。
Just try it. Here.
試試看吧。來。
Come on.
來嘛。
I ordered that wagyu.
我點了那個和牛。
When is that going to get here?
什麼時候才會來？
Oh, not soon enough.
噢，還不夠快。
So it's too bad your boyfriend couldn't make it.
真可惜你男朋友不能來。
That silver spoon thinks he's too good for us, Tink.
那個銀湯匙覺得我們配不上他，小叮噹。
No, he doesn't.
不，他沒有。
You barely even know him.
你幾乎不認識他。
Oh, right.
噢，對啊。
He gave you that big black credit card
他給了你那張大黑信用卡
so you could pay for all of it.
這樣你就能付清所有帳單了。
Which was very kind of him.
他真是太好了。
So when are you all getting married?
那你们什么时候结婚呢？
Oh, we aren't.
哦，我们不打算结婚。
Oh?
哦？
Yeah, we're happy with the way things are.
是的，我们对现在的关系很满意。
Oh.
哦。
Little Dougie's last name is going to be Chase Scola.
小Dougie的姓氏会是Chase Scola。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
It'll be a hard time getting that on the back of a football jersey, huh?
要把这个印在橄榄球衣的背面可不容易，对吧？
Maybe it won't go on the back of a football jersey.
也许它不会出现在橄榄球衣的背面。
What?
什么？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Who knows what Dougie's going to want to do, Dad?
谁知道Dougie将来想做什么呢，爸爸？
I don't want him to get a TBI.
我不想让他得脑震荡。
Or do anything like the way that I grew up.
或者像我小时候那样做任何类似的事情。
What exactly was wrong with the way you grew up, Marina?
玛丽娜，你成长的方式到底有什么问题？
Nina, please, Daddy.
尼娜，拜托，爸爸。
Everything.
一切。
Everything was wrong with the way I grew up.
我成长的方式一切都错了。
I couldn't get away from home fast enough.
我恨不得马上离开家。
I gave you a good life.
我给了你美好的生活。
Keep telling yourself that.
继续这样告诉自己吧。
Keep telling yourself it was a great life, Dad.
继续告诉自己那是个美好的生活，爸爸。
Well, I want a different life for my son,
好吧，我希望我的儿子能过上不同的生活，
and I am damned to die.
我该死。
I'm going to die.
我要死了。
我快要死了。
I'm going to die.
Come on, Tink.
来吧，小叮当。
I said come on, Tink!
我说来吧，小叮当！
I'm so sorry.
我非常抱歉。
You know, this is
你知道，这是
just all going to blow over.
一切都会过去的。
Yeah, I'm okay
是的，我没事。
if it doesn't.
如果事情没有过去。
[music]
[音乐]